every day when I come to work here I
think about the sweet possibility that I
might die since I've never been very
fond of my family I decided to do the
responsible thing and get my Affairs in
order by letting you my fans write my
will in our latest installment of twit
and by here's how I started it please be
compassionate when writing my will I
Daniel TSH hereby being of questionable
mind and sexual
orientation Beque my dildo collection to
my own
butthole I will let you know that within
about 3 hours I received close to 3 or
4,000 references to what I would do with
my dildos etc etc the reason we chose
this one is because it was the first one
that came in in under 8
seconds I give forth my five grow houses
across the United States to those little
kids in Africa who smoking on
swag donate my body to any gay science
I donate everything to the Patrick sesy
foundation in support of ass cancer
karate and
dancing what is half of nothing leave
that to my
mom my television show shall go to Chris
Rock because his five-minute guest spot
had better ratings than my first two
seasons
combined waffles waffles crispy golden
waffles will be stuffed and mounted like
your
mom after death
burn hereby give my collection of
celebrity seamen samples to Ben and
Jerry's for a new series of flavors
called Tosh point oh
faces I know a school teacher that would
love that flavor I do I do he was my
favorite teacher he was totally
misunderstood blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah something racist # High
fashion I Beque my scarf collection to
norf Turner so he can finally cover up
that gross scrotum neck you think norf
was at home goingon night oh twitting by
I'm going to get a
shot I give up on whe writing this
is too hard I leave nothing to nobody
bury my with me if you want nice things
get your own don't wait for me to
die I'm going to get that notorized this
week